In an earlier video, I've written down a form for the cost function for
在前面的视频中 我已经分析了逻辑回归的代价函数
logistical regression.
的表达式
In this optional video, I want to give you a quick justification for
在这节选修视频中 我将给出一个简洁的证明
why we like to use that cost function for logistic regression.
来说明逻辑回归代价函数的表达式为什么是这种形式
To quickly recap, in logistic regression,
回想一下 在逻辑回归中
we have that the prediction y hat is sigmoid of w transpose x + b,
需要预测的结果y~ 可以表示为sigmod(w^T*x + b)
where sigmoid is this familiar function.
sigmoid是我们熟悉的S型函数sigmoid(z)=1/(1+e^-z)
And we said that we want to interpret y hat as the p( y = 1 | x).
我们约定 y~=p(y = 1 | x)
So we want our algorithm to output y hat as the chance
y~=p(y = 1 | x) 即算法的输出y~
that y = 1 for a given set of input features x.
是给定训练样本x条件下 y 等于1的概率
So another way to say this is that if y is equal to 1
换句话说 如果y=1
then the chance of y given x is equal to y hat.
在给定训练样本x条件下 y等于y~
And conversely if y is equal to 0 then
反过来说 如果y=0
the chance that y was 0 was 1- y hat, right?
在给定训练样本x条件下 y等于1减去y~(y=1-y~)
So if y hat was a chance, that y = 1,
因此 如果y~ 代表y=1的概率
then 1-y hat is the chance that y = 0.
那么1-y~ 就是y=0的概率
So, let me take these last two equations and just copy them to the next slide.
接下来 我们就来分析这两个条件概率公式
So what I'm going to do is take these two equations which
这两个条件概率公式定义
basically define p(y|x) for the two cases of y = 0 or y = 1.
形式为p(y|x) 并且代表了 y=0 或者 y=1 这两种情况
And then take these two equations and summarize them into a single equation.
我们可以将这两个公式合并成一个公式
And just to point out y has to be either 0 or 1 because when binary cost equations,
需要指出的是我们讨论的是二分类问题的代价函数
so y = 0 or 1 are the only two possible cases, all right.
因此 y的取值只能是 0 或者 1
When someone take these two equations and summarize them as follows.
上述的两个条件概率公式可以合并成 p(y|x)=(y~)^y*[1-(y~)]^(1-y)
Let me just write out what it looks like, then we'll explain why it looks like that.
接下来 我会解释为什么可以合并成 这种形式的表达式
So (1 – y hat) to the power of (1 – y).
(1-y~) 的 (1-y) 次方
So it turns out this one line summarizes the two equations on top.
因此这行表达式包含了上面的两个条件概率公式
Let me explain why.
我来解释一下为什么这行包含了上面两个条件概率公式
So in the first case, suppose y = 1, right?
第一种情况 假设 y=1
So if y = 1 then this term ends up being y hat,
由于y=1 那么(y~)^y = y~
because that's y hat to the power of 1.
因为 y~ 的 1 次方 等于 y~
This term ends up being 1- y hat to the power of 1- 1, so that's the power of 0.
(1-y~)^(1-y) 的 指数项(1-y)等于0
But, anything to the power of 0 is equal to 1, so that goes away.
由于任何数的0次方都是1 y~乘以1 等于y~
And so, this equation, just as p(y|x) = y hat, when y = 1.
因此当y=1时 p(y|x)=y~
So that's exactly what we wanted.
这就是最终的结果
Now how about the second case, what if y = 0?
第二种情况 当y=0时 p(y|x)等于多少呢?
If y = 0, then this equation above is p(y|x) = y hat to the 0,
假设y=0 y~的y次方 就是 y~的0次方
but anything to the power of 0 is equal to 1, so
任何数的0次方都等于1
that's just equal to 1 times 1- y hat to the power of 1- y.
因此 p(y|x)=1*(1-y~)^(1-y)
So 1- y is 1- 0, so this is just 1.
前面假设y=0 因此1-y就等于1
And so this is equal to 1 times (1- y hat) = 1- y hat.
因此p(y|x) = 1*(1-y~) = 1-y~
And so here we have that the y = 0,p(y|x) = 1- y hat,
因此在这里当y=0时 p(y|x)=1-y~
which is exactly what we wanted above.
这就是这个公式(第二个公式)的结果
So what we've just shown is that this equation
因此 刚才的推导表明p(y|x)=(y~)^y * (1-y~)^(1-y)
is a correct definition for p(ylx).
就是p(y|x)的完整定义
Now, finally because the log function is a strictly monotonically
由于 log 函数是严格单调递增的函数
increasing function, you're maximizing log(p(y|x)) give you similar result
最大化 log(p(y|x)) 等价于
that is optimizing p(y|x) and if you compute log of p(y|x),
最大化 p(y|x) 并且地计算 p(y|x)的 log对数
that's equal to log of y hat r of y 1- y at sub par of 1- y.
就是计算 log((y~)^y * (1-y~)^(1-y)) (其实就是将p(y|x)代入)
And so that simplifies to y log y hat
通过对数函数化简为
+ 1-y times log 1- y hat, right?
y*logy~ + (1-y)*log(1-y~)
And so this is actually negative of the loss
而这就是我们前面提到的
function that we had to find previously.
代价函数的负数(-L(y~,y))
And there's a negative sign there because usually if you're training a learning
前面有一个负号的原因是 当你训练学习算法时
algorithm, you want to make probabilities large
需要算法输出值的概率是最大的（以最大的概率 预测这个值）
whereas in logistic regression we're expressing this.
然而在逻辑回归中
We want to minimize the loss function.
我们需要最小化损失函数
So minimizing the loss corresponds to maximizing the log of the probability.
因此最小化损失函数 与 最大化条件概率的对数（log(p(y|x))）关联起来了
So this is what the loss function on a single example looks like.
因此这就是单个训练样本的损失函数表达式
How about the cost function,
这个损失函数
the overall cost function on the entire training set on m examples?
在m个训练样本的整个训练集中又该如何表示呢?
Let's figure that out.
让我们一起来探讨一下
So, the probability of all the labels In the training set.
整个训练集中的样本值(label 要么是0，要么是1) 的概率
Writing this a little bit informally.
更正式地
If you assume that the training examples I've drawn independently or drawn IID,
假设所有的训练样本服从同一分布且相互独立
identically independently distributed,
也即 独立同分布的
then the probability of the example is the product of probabilities.
所有这些样本的联合概率就是每个样本概率的乘积
The product from i = 1 through m p(y(i) ) given x(i).
从1到m的 给定每个训练样本x^i条件下 y^(i) 的概率乘积
And so if you want to carry out maximum likelihood estimation, right,
要想求解 概率累积(m个样本的概率乘积) 的最大似然估计
then you want to maximize the, find the parameters that maximizes
需要寻找一组参数 使得在训练集中
the chance of your observations in the training set.
给出的样本出现的概率最大
But maximizing this is the same as maximizing the log, so
由于最大化 概率累积 等价于 最大化 概率累积的对数
we just put logs on both sides.
在等式两边取对数
So log of the probability of the labels in the training set is equal to,
训练集中的样本值出现的概率的对数 等于
log of a product is the sum of the log.
对 每个样本的条件概率p(y^i|x^i)的对数 求和
So that's sum from i=1 through m of log p(y(i)) given x(i).
也即从1到m对 log(p(y^i|x^i)) 求和
And we have previously figured out on the previous
在前面视频中我们讲过
slide that this is negative L of y hat i, y i.
它就等于 -L((y~)^i, y^i)
And so in statistics, there's a principle called the principle of maximum likelihood
在统计学里面 有一个方法叫做最大似然估计
estimation, which just means to choose the parameters that maximizes this thing.
即 求出一组参数 使得表达式 取最大值
Or in other words, that maximizes this thing.
或者说 使似然函数取最大值
Negative sum from i = 1 through m L(y hat ,y) and
负1乘以从 1到m 对L((y~)^i, y^i)求和
just move the negative sign outside the summation.
可以将负号移到求和符号的外面
So this justifies the cost we had for
至此 已经验证了前面给出的逻辑回归的代价函数J(w,b)
logistic regression which is J(w,b) of this.
与这里 得到 的形式是一致的(这里从概率的角度解释了代价函数：
最大化训练样本集出现的概率就相当于最小化代价函数)
And because we now want to minimize the cost instead of maximizing likelihood,
由于训练模型时 是求解最小化代价函数 而不是最大化似然函数
we've got to rid of the minus sign.
因此去掉这里的负号
And then finally for convenience, we make sure that our quantities are better scale,
最终为了化简代价函数 可以对代价函数进行适当的缩放
we just add a 1 over m extra scaling factor there.
在前面乘以 (1/m) 的一个常数因子
But so to summarize, by minimizing this cost function J(w,b) we're really
总结一下 为了最小化代价函数J(w,b) 我们
carrying out maximum likelihood estimation with the logistic regression model.
从逻辑回归模型的最大似然估计的角度出发
Under the assumption that our training examples were IID, or
在训练集中的样本都是独立同分布的条件下，将
identically independently distributed.
(将最大似然估计 与 代价函数等价起来)
So thank you for watching this video, even though this is optional.
尽管这节课是选修性质的 但还是感谢观看本节视频
I hope this gives you a sense of why we use the cost function we do for
我希望通过本节课您能更好地明白逻辑回归的代价函数
logistic regression.
为什么是那种形式
And with that, I hope you go on to the exercises, the pre exercise and
明白了代价函数的原理 希望您能继续完成前面课程的练习
the quiz questions of this week.
以及本周的测验
And best of luck with both the quizzes, and the following exercise
在课后的小测验和编程练习中 祝您好运